(15年前)
嗯…我的射箭术挺不错的
So... l'm pretty good at archery.
假如你有时光机
That'll be useful if you ever have a time machine
让你回到中古时期 这对你会很有用
and your time machine breaks, and you're stuck in the Medieval Ages.
你很搞笑，好怪哦
You're funny. lt's weird.
是啊，我很怪
Yeah. l'm weird.
我也是
Me too.
才怪大家都喜欢你 你爸又超有名
Yeah, right. Everyone loves you and your dad's like famous, or something.
我爸妈要离婚 所以我才会参加夏令营
My parents are getting a divorce, that's why l had to go to camp, so...
你在哭吗？ 没有
- Are you crying? - No.
天啊
Jesus.
听好…我不是感情丰富的女生
Look... l'm not really an affectionate person.
情侣注定不会永远在一起
People aren't meant to be together forever.
你真的这么想？
You think so?
真的
Yeah.
我能摸你那里吗？
Can l finger you?
不行
No.
好吧
OK.
(5年前)
- Come on, baby, l got ya! - Don't drop me!
Hey! Hey!
派翠丝！
Patrice!
欧麦尬！我说这是睡衣派对
Oh, my God! l told you that this was a pajama party.
但是你穿的是什么？
What are you wearing? What is this?
你真的穿了连身睡衣？ 搞什么？
You're wearing actual long johns? What?!
这是兄弟会派对
This is a frat party.
你要喝醉才会性感火辣
You just have to be drunk and look hot.
学着点儿吧
Watch and learn.
(婊子)
Hey. Hey!
我醉到超high的！
l'm so drunk!
Drink! Drink! Drink...!
你认识那个女生吗？
Hey, do you know that girl?
那个性感拓荒者？
The sexy pioneer?
我想我认识她
l think l know her.
我会和拓荒者上床，肯定会
l'd have sex with a pioneer. For sure.
尤其是迷路的拓荒者
A hungry pioneer lost on the trail.
我认识你吗？ 嗨，夏令营的亚当法兰克林
- Do l know you? - Hi, Adam Franklin of Camp Weehawken.
我是艾玛柯兹曼 你那时候想摸我那里
l'm Emma Kurtzman. You tried to finger me?
对哦，哇塞！
Yeah. Wow! Do you go here? Why...?
你也念这间大学吗？ 不，我念麻省理工学院
- What are you doing at a party of frat? - No. l go to MlT,
但家里有事，我在这里长大
but l have this family thing, and l grew up in Ann Arbor.
麻省理工学院？ 你长大后比我聪明好多
MlT? Wow. So you grew up to be a lot smarter than me.
有时候我的颈肩很酸
Yeah, sometimes my neck gets sore.
为什么？ 我的脑容量太大了
- Why? - 'Cause my brain's so big.
我同意，没有用，算了
l agree, it didn't work. Drop it.
我喜欢你
l like you.
为什么？你根本就不了解我
What? Why? You don't even know me.
我就是喜欢你
l like you.
我明天得参加一场很蠢的场合 想跟我一起去吗？
l have to go to this stupid thing tomorrow. You wanna come with me?
好啊，我跟你一起去
Yeah, sure. l'll come with you.
什么场合？ 很蠢的场合
- What is it? - Some stupid thing.
我最后想和大家分享
l wanted to leave you with something David said to me
大卫几乎每天都跟我说的话
almost every day at the lab.
他引用爱因斯坦
lt's Einstein.
人有两种过生活的方式
''There are only two ways to live your life.
一种是假设没有奇迹
One, as if nothing is a miracle.
另一种是一切都是奇迹
The other, as if everything is a miracle.''
对大卫来说 最大的奇迹就是他的家人
For David, there was no bigger miracle than his family.
他的女儿艾玛和凯蒂 还有他的太太珊卓
His daughters, Emma and Katie, and his wife, Sandra.
Mom?
妈…这是亚当
l want you to meet Adam.
很遗憾
l'm so sorry.
我老妹凯蒂和她情人凯文
And this is my sister, Katie, and her lover, Kevin.
是男友，也是我的知己
Boyfriend. And my best friend.
谢谢你 我不知道你交了男友
Oh, well... thank you. l didn't know you were dating someone, Emma.
并没有
Oh, l'm not.
我只是14岁跟他发生过一夜情
l just had a one-night stand with him when l was 14.
很感人的葬礼
lt was a really nice funeral.
很遗憾
l'm sorry.
很高兴你留下来
l'm glad you stayed.
我也是
Me too.
我再打给你
So, l'll call you, or something...
亚当，你人很好
Adam, you're wonderful.
幸运的话，你再也不会见到我
lf you're lucky, you're never gonna see me again.
(1年前)
Yes.
Hey.
我们是不是…？我们是大学同学
Did we...? Yes, we did. We went to college together.
你有一对同志爸爸
You have two gay dads.
我是有一对同志爸爸的家伙
Yeah, l'm the man with the two gay dads.
我大二那年他们帮我搬家
They helped me move my boxes sophomore year.
他们超赞，我爱他们 但我是超级异性恋
They're the best. l love them. l'm super straight, though.
好吧
- So, yeah. - OK.
派翠丝，对吧？
- You're Patrice, right? - Yes.
我是伊莱，我和…亚当！
Yeah, Eli. l'm with... Adam!
我马上回来
l'll be right back.
买一些德式爆米花
Pick up some of that kettle corn.
是派翠丝耶
- lt's Patrice. - Hey!
- Patrice! Hey! - How are you?
- Weird. - Wow.
我好久没见到你…
l haven't seen you in... wow.
你好吗？ 很好
- How are you? - Good.
亚当
Adam.
艾玛
Emma.
这是大团圆吗？
What is this, the Peach Pit?
我说的是《飞越比佛利》 对，你也是超级异性恋
- And, yeah, that was a 90210 reference. - Yeah, you're super straight.
你怎么会在这里？ 我刚搬来
- What are you doing here? - l just moved here a week ago.
我在西木教学医院当住院医师
l'm doing my residency at the Westwood Teaching Hospital.
凡娜莎，这是艾玛
- Hi. - Vanessa, this is Emma.
艾玛，凡娜莎 嗨，你好吗？
- Emma, Vanessa. - Hi. How do you do?
这是我们的朋友派翠丝
This is our friend, Patrice.
你好吗？ 让我想想看
- Hi. How do you do? - How do l what?
- Hi. - Hi.
你看起来好漂亮
Hi, you look nice.
很高兴认识你
lt's nice to meet you.
你记得我老妹凯蒂吧 她才刚毕业
You remember my sister, Katie. She's just finishing school here.
好久不见， 自从…
Yeah. l haven't seen you guys since...
爸爸的葬礼
- Yeah, Dad's funeral. - Dad's funeral.
喔，真可怜
Sad.
好了，我们该走了
OK. Well, we should head out, so...
我们也该走了
Yeah, we should, too. You know...
我们应该聚聚，把号码给我
But we should hang out. Let me just... l'll get your number.
把手机给我，我直接输入
Yeah, just give me your phone. l'll put it in there.
好，这样更简单
Yeah, that's probably easier.
我们真的得走了，所以…
We really have to be somewhere now, so...
我们该…
Yeah. We should...
没问题，没问题
Totally. Totally.
很高兴能碰面和见到你们
All right, well, good to hang out. - Good seeing you guys. Have fun. - Yeah.
保重 保重了，各位
- Take care. - Take care, ladies.
我是女五，我有你的钥匙
你说我是你的最爱
她爱我
(现在)
她把爱心刻在树上
女生当家 我们应该积极争取我们想要的
不只这么多
男生走吧，不必看这场秀
我们早就看过
不只这么多
对你不好的男孩要他干嘛？
害你等整晚的男孩要他干嘛？
明明开开心心，干嘛垂头丧气
卡！
And cut!
棒呆了
- Great. - That's good.
- OK! Yeah! - Great. Great.
大伙儿，再来一次 休息5分钟
OK, guys, we're gonna do this again. All right? Five minutes.
- All right, let's... - Good job.
干得好，干得好
- Great job. Great job... - Wait. What are, people...?
班吉，演得好 酷，谢了
- Hey, Benji! Good scene. - Cool. Thanks.
你超帅的！
You looked great!
莎莉，我教你要欲擒故纵
Sari. l told you to play hard to get.
可是我超好把的耶！
l'm incredibly easy to get!
亚当
Adam.
你刚才要问我什么？
You were gonna ask me something before the break.
什么事？
- What was it? - Yeah, l...
靠，到底是什么事？
Wait, wait, wait. Fuck, fuckety-fuck. What was it? Stop.
你要提早收工去见你爸
You wanted to know if you could get off early to see your dad,
没问题，OK的
- which is, yeah, totally fine. - Thank you.
跟你爸说我超爱他的影集
By the way, tell your dad, it's like my favorite show ever.
我有过DVD，弄丢了又买过 棒呆了
Love it, own it, lost it, bought it again. lt's so great.
“我的老天爷！”
''Great Scott!''
你一定成天听到这句话 其实并没有
- You probably hear that all the time. - Not that much.
Yeah.
查克！
Chuck!
再拍自己的鸡鸡我就没收手机
Chuck! lf l catch you taking pictures of your dick one more time, l'm gonna take that thing away.
您好，我能效劳吗？
He//o. How can / he/p you?
菲利普，我是亚当 嗨，请进
- Hey, Philippe, it's Adam. - Hi. Come in.
嗨，爸
- Hey, Dad. - Hey.
你看看
Check it out.
活力瑜珈和蛙人操
Vinyasa yoga and the Army Ranger workout.
我合在一起做 哇，猴塞雷
- l combined them! - Wow. That's very impressive.
我可能会拍DVD，活力蛙人操
l'm gonna do a video, l think. Vinyasa Power.
看得出你的肌肉都练到哪里
l can almost see where your muscles go.
很好笑，揍我
Very funny. Hit me.
不，我不想让你受伤
No, l'm not gonna hit you. l don't want to hurt you.
不会啦 用力揍我一拳
You're not gonna hurt me. Come on, hit me. Give me your best shot.
快点，免得我得疝气
Come on, quick, before l get a hernia!
不要
No.
你说的对，那就哈草吧
You're right. Let's smoke some weed.
(我的老天爷！)
这是上等货 经纪人替我弄了张医疗大麻卡
This is really good stuff. My agent got me one of those medical marijuana cards.
很高兴他们这么尽职
lt's nice to see they're supporting your career.
那部影集录得怎样？
Yeah. So, how's the show going?
很棒，关于一群高中生 又唱又跳又玩部落格
l mean, great. l mean, it's about high-schoolers who sing and dance and blog.
至少你在编剧，这很重要
At least you're writing, that's what's important.
不，我只是助理制作人
No. l'm an assistant.
至少他们看过你的剧本
Well, but... at least they've seen your writing.
还没有
Not yet.
其实…
Actually...
我写了一集，想请你给点意见
l wanted to get your opinion on this episode that l wrote.
这只是初稿
Kind of a sample.
做的好！儿子
That's my boy.
我会先看然后打些电话
l'll take a look at it, sure. And then l'll call somebody.
不，不要打电话 看完了告诉我你觉得怎样
No. Do not call anyone. Just read it and tell me what you think.
好吧
OK.
所以…
So...
你有没有在炒饭？
Are you having sex?
有，我有在炒饭
Yes. l'm having sex.
你有任何疑问
'Cause if you want any pointers, you know...
我很乐意教你 离过两次婚的好处是学会口交
...l can help you out. lf there's one thing you learn after two failed marriages, it's how to eat kitty.
你有女友吗？ 没有
- Anyone special? - No.
自从和凡娜莎分手后就没有
l mean, not since Vanessa.
一年了，你该交新的女友
lt's been a year. lt's time to move on.
才过了8个月
lt's been eight months, Dad.
你到底想跟我谈什么？
What did you want to talk to me about, anyway?
你有养狗吗？ 斑斑！过来！
- You got a dog? Seriously, that's... - Freckles! Come!
你还没告诉他？
You didn't tell him yet?
该死！
Damn!
l...
我想告诉你，我正要告诉你
Adam, l wanted to tell you. l was just about to tell you.
多久？
How long?
什么？ 多久了？
- Well... - How long?
不久，我…
Not long. l...
她需要地方住，房东又是大烂人
She needed a place to stay because, you know, her landlord is such a D-bag.
我在圣诞节派对遇到她
Christmas. l ran into her at a party.
我们开始聊天，聊的都是你
We got to talking. About you, mostly.
看起来很软！
lt looked so soft!
并不软
lt's not. God!
天啊，好痛哦
Oh, that really hurt. Damn.
你在上我的前女友？
You're fucking my ex-girlfriend?
没错，可是…
Well, yeah, but...
她超辣的 我知道她有多辣
- She's just so hot. - l know how hot she is.
你们人真好 去你的！
- That's really sweet. Thanks, guys. - Fuck you!
亚当，我不是个好爸爸
Adam. All right, l'm not the perfect dad.
但我也不能向爱情说不呀
But the worst thing you can do in life is to say no to love.
我觉得她真的很爱我
And l think she really loves me.
别这样，亚当
Don't. Adam.
我的同志爸爸最棒的是什么？
Hey, you know the best part about my gay dads?
What?
他们绝不会替我前女友口交
They're never gonna eat out my ex-girlfriends.
那倒是
That's true.
我听说… 你和你爸变成表兄弟了
Hey, l heard. You and your dad are tunnel buddies, huh?
瓦勒斯！ 她为了你爸甩掉你
- Wow, Wallace! - She chose your dad over you, man.
就好像用卡匣代替iPod
That's like trading an iPod for a 8 track.
你得报一箭之仇 找他的前女友炒饭
You need to get even. Go have sex with one of his ex-girlfriends.
他在高潮的时候会不会大叫
Hey, you think when he's busting a nut,
“我的老天爷！” 不会吗？
he's like, ''Great Scott''? No?
能不能聊别的？什么都行
Wait. Can we talk about something else? Like, literally, anything else?
当然可以
- Yeah. - Of course. Yeah.
我的老天爷
- Great Scott. - OK.
够了，我豁出去了 豁出去什么？
- That's it. l'm going for it. - Going for what?
我要打给手机里的每个女生
l'm gonna call every girl in my phone
直到有一个肯跟我炒饭
until someone agrees to have sex with me.
超屌的，我敬你 这是个自我毁灭的计划
- That's strong. Toast to that. - Toast. That is a terrible, self-destructive plan,
但我们百分百支持你
and we're behind you a hundred percent.
你也好吗？
Well, hello to you!
我可以赶去俄亥俄州
Yeah, l can come to Ohio.
俄亥俄州？不行啦
Ohio? No, you can't.
我搭计程车
l'll take a cab.
好，我去找你
No, it's fine. l'll come to you.
哪间医院？
What hospital?
我现在只需要有人陪
l just really need to be with someone right now.
我在想你能不能让我上你
Hey, l was wondering... Do you have someplace l could put my boner?
我们可以玩抱抱就行
No, it's just... we could just snuggle or something.
你几岁啦？
What? Well, how old are you?
- Oh... - OK.
我行！我行！
l got it! l got it.
我行啦
l got it. l got it.
l got it!
你不记得我的名字了，对吧？
You don't remember my name, do you?
没关系
lt's OK.
我叫希拉 你看起来需要喝咖啡
lt's Shira, and you look like you could use some coffee.
好，咖啡很好
Yes. Coffee's good.
我的…
l got...
我的裤子咧？
Where are my pants?
不知道，可能在任何地方，来
l don't know. They could be anywhere. Here's your coffee.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你昨晚开不开心？
Did you have a good time last night?
还好啦，没什么特别的
lt was all right. Nothing special.
听好，我要你知道
Listen, l want you to know that...
我很尊重你
...l respect you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
通常我都会记得… 跟我那个的人的名字
Normally, l would remember the name of someone that l've...
什么？我的天
What? Oh, my God.
你以为我们炒过饭 拜托，并没有，好吗？
Did you think we had sex? Oh, my God, we did not have sex.
亚当，你把袜子留在我房间
Hey, Adam. You left your socks in my room.
有吗？ 有
- Did l? - You did.
我有没有把裤子留在你房间？
Did l, by chance, leave my pants in your room?
没，我见到你的时候 你就没穿裤子
No. When we met, you weren't wearing pants.
别再逗他了啦，大伙儿
Stop teasing him, you guys.
派翠丝，我认识你
- Patrice. Hey, l know you. - Hey.
- Yeah. - OK.
昨晚发生什么事？
What happened last night?
我们有没有…？ 我们有炒饭，而且我很爽
- Did we do it? - We had sex. Yeah. l really liked it.
我不知道我的身体能承受那种痛
l didn't know that my body could handle that much pain.
可是我喜欢
And that l would like it.
你醒啦！
You're up.
艾玛
Emma.
你也住在这里？ 对
- You live here? - Yep.
感觉好一点吗？
You feeling any better?
我昨晚有没有在这里跟谁炒饭？
Did l have sex with anyone in this apartment last night?
并没有
No, you didn't.
没有，抱歉 你没有
- No. Sorry. - You didn't.
谢谢你们哦，很好笑
Thank you. Yeah, that's... that's funny.
让我们嘲笑宿醉的溜鸟侠
Let's make fun of the hung-over naked guy.
我有你的裤子，想要就跟我来
But l do have your pants, so if you want them, come with me.
好，谢谢你
Yes. Thank you.
别害臊，我们都是医生
You don't have to feel embarrassed, because we're all doctors,
每个礼拜都得看几百根阴茎
so we see literally hundreds of penises a week.
我看过几千根
l see thousands.
我昨天才从宝特瓶拔出一根
l just pulled a penis out of a VitaminWater yesterday.
大家都看习惯了
- So, we are cool with penises here. - OK.
我们是专业医师
We're professionals.
Well...
幸会了
lt has been a pleasure.
好翘的屁股
Bravo.
超翘的
- Nice. - Bravo, bravo.
没错，我绝对是同志
Yep, l'm definitely gay.
我怎么会跑来这里？
So, how did l get here?
你传简讯给我说是紧急事件
You texted me that it was an emergency,
我把地址传给你 然后你就跑来
and then l texted you my address, and then you came over.
我猜你以为你回家了
And l think you thought you were at home,
因为你开始脱衣服
because you started taking off all your clothes.
噢，天啊
Oh, God.
你的裤子 谢了
- Here are your pants. - Thank you.
所以…
So...
我只是昏睡在沙发上？
- Did l just pass out on your couch? - No.
没有，你还干了一件事 有点像是…一种舞
No, then you did this thing. lt was... ...like a dance?
一种舞？ 是啊，像这样
- Dance? - Yeah, like...
我在你面前摇晃我的老二？ 对
- l shook my dick at you? - Yeah.
靠，真是对不起
Oh, shit. l'm sorry.
其实…还蛮刺激的
No, no, it was... it was exciting.
你一边摇晃一边欢呼
lt was like you were cheering while you were doing it.
“喔耶，看看我的老二”
You were like, ''Look at my dick!''
你有看吗？ 当然有
- Did you look at it? - Yeah, l looked.
挺不赖的 你的老二很不错
lt was nice. You have a really nice penis.
不错？ 挺自由自在的
- Nice? - lt seems kind of like carefree.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
老天爷 我不知道该从何说起，我爸…
Jesus. l don't know where to start. My dad's...
我爸在和我前女友交往
My dad's dating my ex-girlfriend.
你昨晚跟我说了
You told me about it last night.
我是不是很有魅力？
Did l tell you like in a charming way?
我是不是又迷人又搞笑
Was l like charming and funny when l told you?
是，你光着屁股大哭特哭
Yeah. You were... ...naked and crying.
Yeah.
我真是一团糟
l'm a mess.
Hey.
不会有事的
lt's gonna be OK.
谢了
Thanks.
我是说真的
Seriously.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我该准备出门了，我不想迟到
l should probably get ready now. l don't want to be late.
好…你不想迟到
Yeah, it's... You don't want to be late.
对，那样不好
No, that would be bad.
保险套？
Condom?
我有保险套
- Condom. Get a condom. - l know. Condoms.
- OK. - Condoms.
有了
Got it.
快点
- Got it. - Hurry.
需要帮忙吗？
You need help?
我能搞定
- l got it. - OK.
好了
Here we go.
你还穿着…
Oh, you got your...
让我来…
- Yep. - Let me just...
- Hey. - Yeah.
我们在炒饭耶 我知道
- We're having sex. - l know.
我们10分钟后要到医院
Emma, we have to be in the hospital in ten minutes.
好啦！
OK.
你只有45秒的时间达到高潮
You have 45 seconds to pull your shit together, OK?
我一定会比你快 很好
- l'm way ahead of you. - Fine.
很好
Fine.
找到了 太好了
- Found it! - Oh, great.
Thank you.
我们不要告诉任何人
So, we're not gonna tell anyone about this, OK?
这样比较简单
- Yeah. Of course. - lt's just easier that way.
当然 很好
- Definitely. - Good.
艾玛！该走了！
Emma, time to go!
来了！
Coming!
- All right? - ls this...?
这样看起来像是炒过饭吗？
- No. - lt looks like something happened.
帐单给我，我买单
l'm gonna get the bill. l'll pay for it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- Hey. - Hey.
Hi.
我只想在传简讯之后打给你
l just wanted to follow up that text with a phone call.
看看你想不想再聚一聚
Wanted to see if you wanted to hang out again.
我饿死了
l'm starving.
怪了，你出现在我在的餐馆前面
That's weird. You just pulled up in front of the restaurant that l'm eating at.
Hey.
Hi.
嗨，我是山姆 我们是同事
- Hey. l'm Sam. - We work together at the hospital.
只有15分钟买午餐
We have like 15 minutes to get food, so...
我有车，她只是利用我
She's just using me for my car.
你是个医生？ 还不是，希望就快是了
- You're a doctor? - Not yet. Fingers crossed.
棒呆了，好样的
Awesome. That's awesome for you.
嗨，伊莱
- Hey, Eli. - Hey.
我们很赶，很高兴见到你
Well, we're kind of in a rush, so it was good seeing you.
幸会了
- Nice to meet you. - Nice meeting you.
你今天很美
You look beautiful today.
幸会了
Nice meeting you.
你这五八蛋
You piece of shit.
怎么了？ 什么怎么了？我问你
- What? - ''What?'' Let me ask you.
你是不是跟艾玛上了床？
Did you have sex with Emma?
没有
No.
你有没有跟艾玛炒饭？
Did you have sex with Emma?
有
Yes.
可是我不该告诉任何人
- l'm not supposed to tell anyone. - Yes! Wow!
我打给她，她没回电 只传了简讯
l called her, but she didn't call me back. She sent me a text.
她写什么？ “嗨”
- All right. Well, what'd she text you? - ''Hi.''
只有“嗨”？没别的？
- Just ''Hi''? - ''Hi.'' With nothing else? Just ''H-i''?
我该怎么回应？
l don't know. What do l do with that? l don't know.
情况不妙
That's not good.
你得赶快抽身，结束了
You just gotta walk away, pal. lt's over.
她对你没兴趣 真的吗？
- She's not into it. - Shit. Seriously?
很高兴见到你们 回头见
- Good seeing you guys. - See you later.
你真以为她是利用他的车？
You really think she's just using him for his car?
才怪，他想在油电车里上她
No, Adam, l don't. l think he wants to fuck her in his Prius.
因为在油电车里面做爱超环保的
And the thing about fucking in a Prius is that you don't have to feel guilty afterwards.
因为可以节能减碳
- 'Cause of the carbon footprint. - Yeah.
梅医师前几天跟我说话 不是吧，他说什么？
- Metzner talked to me the other day. - Shut up. What did he say?
“你做错了”，超棒的
He was like, ''No, you're doing that wrong.'' lt was amazing.
艾玛
Emma.
你跑来干嘛？
What are you doing here?
你没回电，我就自己跑来
Hi. You didn't call me back, so l thought l'd come here.
送你的
lt's for you.
恭喜？恭喜什么？跟你炒饭？
''Congrats''? For what? Having sex with you?
对，你干得很好 我觉得应该送你气球
Yeah. You did a good job, so... l thought you deserved a balloon.
我在工作耶 好吧
- l'm working. - OK.
你干嘛不回我电话？
So, what's up with not calling me back?
我不太会这种事 什么事？聊天？
- l'm not good at this stuff. - At what, talking?
对，聊天，沟通 谈恋爱之类的
Yeah, talking. Communicating. Relationship stuff.
是这样的
lt's just... This is...
要是我们谈恋爱
lf we were in a relationship,
我就会变得很古怪很可怕
l'd become a weird, scary version of myself, and...
我的喉咙会缩紧跳动
My throat starts constricting, the walls start throbbing.
就像花生酱过敏症 感情的花生酱过敏症
lt's like a peanut allergy, like... an emotional peanut allergy.
我也不能跟你交往 你不是我爸的菜
Well, l can't date you, either. 'Cause you're not my dad's type, so...
艾玛，巡房 嗨，亚当
Emma, rounds. Hey, Adam.
我该走了
- What's up? - Look, l should probably go.
谢谢你，我们只是朋友
Thank you. We'll be friends, right?
对，普通朋友
Yeah, friends.
我们的身高差太多
With the height difference?
他站在我旁边好像要绑架我
We stand next to each other, it looks like he's kidnapping me.
干嘛？ 你老是这样
- What? - You always do this.
故意挑喜欢你的男生的毛病
You always find something wrong with everybody who likes you.
我交往过的男生才真正有毛病
And l date guys who have real problems.
有一个偷走我的信用卡
l date guys who steal my credit card,
然后怪我没把信用卡收好
and then they tell me it's my fault because l left it out.
你却找到完美的男生
You find these perfect guys,
然后说:行不通，他太快乐了
and then you're like, ''lt'll never work, he's too happy.''
怎样，梅医师？
What's up, Dr. Metzner?
我跟梅大医师说“怎样”？
Did l just say ''What's up'' to Stephen Metzner?
真是惨不忍睹
That was really hard to watch.
我知道我应该想要谈恋爱
Look, l know l'm supposed to want to be in a relationship.
不过到头来我只会心碎 留下一堆他的旧T恤
But l'd just end up with a broken heart and a bunch of his old T-shirts.
逻辑上来说… 你在干嘛？
- Just from a purely logical aspect... - What are you doing?
传简讯给他 当然了
- l'm texting him. - Of course you are.
你有女生问题，我很同情你
我有99个问题，不包括女生
你不该送她气球
You know, you shouldn't have gotten her a balloon actually.
你是“天外奇迹”的老头吗？
Who do you think you are, the old guy from Up?
你叫我送她气球
You told me to get her a balloon.
我没想到你真的会送，逊毙了
Well, l didn't think you'd actually do it. lt's a terrible idea.
没人知道这件事，别说出去 不会啦
Listen. Hey, nobody knows about this, - so don't say anything to anyone. OK? - All right, l won't.
艾玛传的简讯 上面写什么？
- lt's from Emma. - What's it say?
“你在哪里？” 你写什么？
- ''Where are you?'' - What are you writing?
“嗨，你好”和一个眯眼
''Hi, how are you doing?'' and then a winky face.
亚当，过了晚上10点了
No, Adam, it's after 10pm.
“你在哪里？”的意思是:
Come on, the ''Where are you?'' text is like saying:
我想炒饭
''Hey, l want to have sex with you,
但是我得知道你有多醉
but l just need to know how drunk you are.''
Hey.
你上了艾玛然后送她气球？
Did you fuck Emma and then bring her a balloon?
什么？你告诉他？
What? Did you tell him?
没！有！
No! Yes!
你不能告诉任何人 她传简讯给他: “你在哪里？”
- You can't tell anyone. - She just texted him, ''Where are you?''
她想要炒饭
Oh, she wants the dick.
亚当，你得Man一点 一定要有威严
Adam, you want to come back strong here. Go from a position of power.
回传说: “我在哪里？我在你“那里””
Something like, ''Where am l? Why don't you check your underpants.''
对，别这样写
- Yeah. Don't write that. - Yeah!
我才不会咧 我喜欢吓人
- l would never write that. - See, l like to be kind of scary.
像是“砰，我的老二来了”
Like, ''Boo! Here comes my dick.''
你和女生炒完饭送她气球？
Did you have sex with some girl and give her a balloon?
你能不能不要告诉每个人呀？
Can we not tell everyone?
我道歉
l apologize.
你回传什么？
So, what'd you write back?
“嗨”
''Hi.''
这样还行 不错，很好
- Yeah, that could work. - Yeah, it's not bad. ''Hi'' is fine.
(你家半小时后)
你做了很多有趣的动作
There were so many interesting things going on.
翻转的动作，那算什么？
- Yeah. - That flippy thing, what was that?
不知道，我突然想到就做了
Sure, l just, l don't know, l had an idea, l just went with it.
那真的很棒 谢谢你
- That was a really good call. - Thank you.
我们最好不要抱抱
We probably shouldn't snuggle.
好，感觉不对劲
Yeah. That just felt wrong.
我该走了
l should head out.
这么快？ 是啊
- Already? - Yeah.
你想吃松糕吗？
You want to grab a muffin or something?
不行，我得工作
l can't. l have to go to work.
我不想吓到你，不过…
OK. You know, l don't want to freak you out, but...
改天我想跟你在白天约会
...l'd love to hang out with you in the daytime sometime.
不可能，我没时间
lt's not really possible. l have no time.
我每周工作80小时 轮班36小时
l work 80 hours a week, doing 26-hour shifts.
我需要的是半夜两点跟我上床
What l need is someone who's gonna be in my bed at 2am,
不会说谎 也不必跟他吃早餐的男人
who l don't have to lie to or eat breakfast with.
我超讨厌吃早餐，还有说谎
l hate breakfast. And lying.
我也讨厌战争
l also hate war.
你想这样吗？
Do you want to do this?
怎么样？
Do what?
利用对方做爱做的事 24小时随时待命
Use each other for sex, at all hours of the day and night.
其它的什么都不做
Nothing else.
行，我可以 很好
- Yeah, l could do that. - Good.
这一定会很好玩
lt's gonna be fun.
这一定行不通 为什么？
- You know this is never gonna work. - Why not?
因为你会爱上我
Because clearly you're gonna fall in love with me.
是吗？ 那就等到
Oh, really? Well, then we just do this
其中一个动了感情 然后就停下来
until one of us feels something more, and then we stop.
不会是我 也不会是我
- Well, it won't be me. - lt won't be me.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
- Hey. - Hey.
我们是炮友
We're sex friends.
我们只是饭饭之交
Just friends who have sex.
这是不可能的
That's not possible.
我要发剧本…要花一个小时
l'm going to distribute these for an hour or so.
我们应该保持简单
Listen, we should keep this simple.
也许应该建立基本规则
l mean, maybe we should establish some ground rules.
基本规则，好主意
Ground rules. Good idea.
可以先从不吵架开始
OK, well, we can start with no fighting.
不说谎 都很好
- No lying. - Those are good ones.
不吃醋，直视对方的眼睛
No jealousy, no staring deeply into each other's eyes.
别把我列为紧急联络人 反正我人会到
Don't list me as your emergency contact. l won't come.
这不是违反医生职业道德吗？
lsn't that against your Hippocratic oath?
- Yeah. - Yeah?
我不会让你死 是吗？
- l'd let you die. - Oh, yeah?
我一小时后回来
l'll be back in like... an hour.
玩得开心
Have fun.
我只是去买优格
l'm just getting some yogurt.
天啊，我败犬到想骂人
God, l am single as fuck.
天啊，它好像直直往我凸过来
Oh, my God. lt looks like it's coming right at me.
还有，别说我的老二很可爱
Hey, one more thing. Don't call my penis cute.
就算它扮成小熊温柔地看着你
Even if it's dressed up like a Care Bear, and it's giving you a Care Stare.
别打扮你的老二，千万不要
Don't dress up your penis. Ever.
你的保险给付侵入性手术吗？
Does your insurance cover invasive procedures?
这游戏有点太可怕了
OK. OK, this is getting a little too realistic.
相信我
Trust me.
有人到处在嘿咻 害我不能专心看A片！
l can't focus on my porn with all this real sex going on around me!
Yes, l'm ready.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?!
我寄了交友邀请，你会接受吗？
l just friended you. Do you think you're gonna confirm or ignore?
我一定不会接受
Oh, l'm gonna confirm. For sure.
你这么漂亮，当然会啰
Yeah, look at you. Of course.
需要帮忙吗？
Anytime. Need some help?
太好了！太好了！
Oh, beautiful! Beautiful!
(他的手真的很小)
...the tomatoes are Australian.
那算什么？ 什么？
- What was that? - What?
你在吃醋吗？ 那家伙？拜托
- Are you being jealous? - Of that guy? Come on.
就算我喜欢他，我们也会变
Look, even if l did like him, it doesn't change what we're doing.
喔，所以你不喜欢他啰 亚当，我是你女友
- Ah, so you like him. - Adam, l'm not yours.
当然了，我怎么会这么想？
No, of course not. Why would l think that?
哇，油电车耶，水哦
Wow. Prius. Nice.
有点娘，不过很赞 你开什么车？
- lt's kind of girly, but nice, huh? - What do you drive?
老旧的BMW，5系列，那里
Just an old BMW. Five series. Right there.
是喔，我不是自己买的
Oh, yeah, sure. l actually paid for mine.
是父母给的
l didn't take it from my parents.
我也不是自己买的
Yeah, l paid for mine, too.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
你的块头很大，有健身吗？
You're a big guy. Do you work out?
我划
Oh. l row.
划船吗？
Like boats?
我在哈佛大学是划船队 哈佛大学！
- l rowed crew at Harvard. - Oh, Harvard.
你算是头儿？是不是这样叫？
What were you, a cocksman? What do they say?
我是船长
- What do they call it? - Coxswain.
我很了，你跟艾玛上床
No. You know, l get it, right? That you're sleeping with Emma?
什么？
l what?
你和艾玛炒饭，我了了
That you and Emma have sex sometimes. l get it.
她累了就打给你 你开车过来炒饭…我猜10分钟
She's tired, she calls you up, you drive over, and have sex for, l'm guessing, ten minutes.
你觉得会持久吗？
Think that's gonna last?
我不知道你在说什么
l don't know what you're talking about.
才怪，现在是没问题啦
Sure you do. And that's fine, for now.
不过我才会每天陪在她身边
But you should just know that l'm gonna be there right next to her every day,
当个医生…救人济世
using big words... ...saving people's lives.
当她厌倦了你就会奔到
Then, when she's done having her fun with you, she's gonna
我怀里 因为我是大人，有真正的工作
come running to me, because l'm a grownup, and l have a real job.
我真的能照顾她，了吗？
l can actually take care of her, you know?
我是她要嫁的男人
l'm the guy she marries, Adam.
你只能跟她在残障厕所炒饭
You're the guy she fucked a couple of times in the handicapped bathroom.
这是什么？ 我的脚呀，亚当
- What's this? - These are my feet, Adam.
超难看的 不，这个啦
- They're fantastic. - No, this.
那是你的剧本
That's your script.
你爸要我拿给你
Your dad told me to give it to you.
他看了，写了些意见
Yeah, he read it, and he gave you notes, and...
我会说艾文跟我嗑了魔菇
l'm not saying Alvin and l did mushrooms together,
但我也不会说有
but l'm not prepared to say that we didn't.
我知道你们父子之间没问题
l know that you have issues with your dad, and that's cool,
但他真的喜欢你，他也喜欢我
but he really likes you and he definitely likes me,
我们在脑力激荡，随便瞎掰
and we were just jamming ideas and goofing around
嗑药嗑到超high的
and tripping our balls off.
我要你跳得更悍一点
Hey. So... l really feel like it needs to be more ghetto.
就像狂客舞
You know, like, more crunk? Can you work it out? Thanks.
跳得不错
- Hey. Nice moves. - Hey.
我知道你很努力，但不够好
l know you were trying really hard out there, but it just didn't work.
你能不能…嗯，我…
Hey, would you ever...? l...
我写了一集的剧本
l wrote an episode.
我念大学的时候会创作
- l used to write in college, so... - OK.
我得阻止你 那是你的工作
l'm gonna have to stop you right there. - Not your job. - Yeah.
我是真的会读东西的怪胎
Hey. l'm, like, actually one of those freaks who reads things,
你想给我看没问题
so if you wanted to give it to me, that's cool.
真的吗？ 真的
- Really? - Yeah.
谢谢你 不客气
- Thank you. - Sure.
梅根有时候会听我的
Megan listens to me. Sometimes.
薇多莉亚！ 拜托，我看到你抽烟
Victoria! Seriously? Like, l can see you smoking right there.
给我熄掉！我不会追你
Put it out! l'm not gonna chase you.
我不会…薇多莉亚！
l'm not gonna... l'm not gonna... Victoria! Hey!
艾玛！
Emma!
没事吧？我收到你的简讯
Katie, is everything OK? l got your message.
艾玛，我有很棒的消息
Emma, l have really good news.
昨天野餐后发生的
OK, it happened yesterday after the picnic,
但是我想当面告诉你
but l wanted to tell you in person.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我要结婚了！
l'm getting married.
l'm getting married!
我要结婚了！耶！
- You're getting married. - l'm getting married!
妈超兴奋的
Mom is so excited.
她昨晚又哭又叫
She was like screaming and crying last night.
她要跟骨头飞来帮我挑婚纱
And she's gonna fly down with Bones and help me shop for the dress.
骨头？谁是骨头？
With who? ''Bones''? Who's Bones?
噢，靠 凯蒂，谁是骨头？
- Oh, crap. - Katie, who's Bones?
他是妈的朋友
He's Mom's friend.
我应该告诉你的，靠
l wasn't supposed to tell you about it. Crap.
她有了男朋友？他叫骨头？
She has a boyfriend? Named Bones?
他不是游民吗？ 是啦！
- What is he, a drifter? - No.
她为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't she tell me?
艾玛
Well, Emma...
你习惯一个人，我和妈像你
You're so good at being alone. Mom and l aren't like that.
那是什么意思？ 是真的
- What's that supposed to mean? - lt just is true.
听我说，凯蒂
Look, Katie.
你才22岁，你真的要退学…
You're 22. Do you really think you're ready to quit school...?
我爱他
l love him.
喝热茶会减缓经痛
Tea for your 'gina.
我老妹要结婚了
Thanks. My sister's getting married.
我们知道 我们听说了
- Yes, we know that. - We heard.
闭嘴，艾玛
Oh, shut up, Emma.
你有吃普拿疼吗？
Did you take your Pamprin?
不要管我 你才不要管我
- Leave me alone. - You leave me alone.
我最爱我们的月经同时来
l love it when we're all on the same cycle.
这样就能名正言顺吵架
We all get to be passive-aggressive and fight.
你又不是女人
You are not even a woman.
哪是谁？
Who is that?
谁？
Hello?
我是亚当
Hey, it's Adam.
开什么玩笑？
Are you kidding me?
走开
Go away.
我有杯子蛋糕
l've got cupcakes.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
我叫你不要来，这里不安全
l told you not to come. lt's not safe in here.
有没有红丝绒口味？
Do you think that you have red velvet in there?
也许有
l might.
咱们看看有什么口味
Let's take a look and see what we have here.
希拉，巧克力蛋糕 快点
Shira, chocolate. Now.
我知道这是怎么回事 你们的MC同时来
l understand what's going on. You're all on the same cycle.
这超令人兴奋的
This is very exciting.
接下来3到5天 你们的子宫内膜会剥落
Your uterine walls will be shedding for the next three to five days.
你是上网查的吗？
Nice memorization. Did you Google that?
也许是
l may have.
因为你们都是女人 这是很美好的事
Because you're women. And l think that's a beautiful thing.
我的裤档就像犯罪现场
lt's like a crime scene in my pants.
我也替你…
Oh. l also...
烧了这片光碟
...made you this.
帮助你抚慰子宫
To help soothe your womb.
这是集锦歌
lt's a mix.
《顺流》、 《红红酒》
''Even Flow,'' ''Red Red Wine.''
《血腥星期天》？
''Sunday Bloody Sunday''?
Adam.
你替我录了月经集锦歌？
Did you make me a period mix?
超浪漫的
That's so romantic.
法兰克辛纳屈
Frank Sinatra.
《我牵住了全世界》
''l've Got The World On A String.''
经典名曲
lt's a classic.
我一直，一直流爱的血
把那鬼东西拿开
Get that shit away from me.
这是浓汤，对你的子宫很好
Come on, it's soup. lt's good for your uterus.
你不喝我就要一直唱
Just take it, or l'm gonna keep singing.
我一直，一直流爱的血
噢，靠
Oh, shit.
嗯，亚当
Oh, Adam.
亚当！
Adam.
What?
我们睡着了，而且是抱着睡
We fell asleep. We were spooning.
真的吗？ 真的
- We were? - Yeah.
而且我们穿着衣服
And we were spooning with our clothes on,
这比没穿更糟糕十倍
which is like ten times worse.
惨了 是啊
- Oh, shit. - Yeah.
穿着衣服抱着睡觉 太糟糕了
- Fully clothed spoon. - This is bad.
我的错，我不该熬汤给你喝
This is my fault. l should not have made you soup.
我们该怎么办？ 什么怎么办？
- What are we gonna do? - About what?
也许我们应该…暂时停下来
Maybe we should... Maybe we should stop for a while.
不，我们不能停下来
No, we're not stopping.
我不晓得耶
Yeah, well, l don't know.
去上别的美眉
Go hook up with someone else.
你是说真的？ 对
- Are you serious? - Yeah, go...
去最近的夜店和陌生人做爱
Go to the nearest bar and have sex with a stranger.
你在开玩笑 并没有
- You're kidding? - No.
这太扯了啦 你替我录了月经集锦歌
- This is crazy. - You made me a period mix.
亚当，这是禁忌耶
Adam, this is an emergency.
你要我走？
- So you just want me to go? - Yeah.
随便跟女人做爱？ 对，快去
- Just have sex with a random woman? - Yeah, go.
一个性感的女人？
Like a sexual woman?
对！
Yes!
我也会去跟别人上床
l'll go have sex with someone, too.
好吧
OK.
这对我们俩都好 是啊，好极了
- No, this is gonna be good for us. - Yeah. lt's great.
太好了，干得好
Great. Well done. Well played.
掰了！
Bye.
我有两星期没跟她见面
l haven't seen her in two weeks, so...
她叫我上别的美眉，怎么办？
She said l should hook up with other people. l mean, what am l supposed to do with that?
看着我的脸 我不了啦，只是…
- Look at my face. - No, l get it. l just...
我的脸在说什么？
Look at my face. What does my face say?
你过着每个男人的梦想生活
Yeah, Adam, come on, you're living every man's dreams.
她要你上别的美眉
l mean, she wants you to hook up with other girls.
十年后你只能上你老婆
- Yes. - Look, in ten years from now, you're gonna be having sex with your wife.
永远是男上女下
And it's gonna be in the missionary position.
而且你们其中一个会睡着
- And one of you is going to be asleep. - Yep.
当你回想到这一刻
And you're gonna think back to this moment,
你会哭着打给我
and you're gonna call me up, crying.
我不会当面笑你 不好意思哦
And l'm gonna laugh in your face, Adam. l'm sorry, but it's what l'm gonna do.
但这是好机会
This is a gift right now.
你甚至不必陪她吃早餐
You don't even have to have breakfast with her.
我不知道，我了啦
l know. l get that. l just...
看着我的脸
Look at my face.
你会带亚当到圣诞节派对吗？
You bringing Adam to the Christmas party tonight?
不会，我们的关系太紧绷 我们各自找到别人才会见面
No. Things were getting too intense, so we decided not to see each other until we hook up with other people.
太好了，今晚有搞头了
OK. Yes. Good. We are getting laid tonight, right?
就像“寻找新方向” 你是主角
This is gonna be like Sideways, except that you're Paul Giamatti,
我是有搞头的配角 我不能有搞头？
- and l'm the guy that gets laid. - l can't get laid?
不行，今晚我超火辣的
No. Tonight is about me, Emma. All right? l'm feeling hot.
我的内裤没洗，只穿丁字裤
l'm feeling good. l am wearing bikini bottoms because my other underwear is dirty.
我们很性感，你觉得呢？
All right, we're hot. You feel hot?
没人吐在我身上
No one threw up on me today.
我们是花痴，超贱的花痴
We're sluts, Emma! We're dirty, dirty, sluts!
记住，我们是花痴
- OK. - Remember, we're sluts!
您好，先生
Good evening, sir.
不，让我来，我来开门
No, l got that! l got that, pal. That's gonna be me.
你刚才替我开车门？ 对
- Did you just open the car door for me? - Yes, l did.
没人替我开过车门，再来一次
No one's ever done that for me before. Do it again.
All right.
怎样？ 棒呆了
- How's that? - lt's amazing.
我能挽着你的手吗？
Can l have your arm?
告诉家属他们挚爱的亲人死了
So, when l have to tell someone that someone they loved died,
真的很难，有时候我会笑
it's hard, you know? Sometimes l laugh.
因为有点尴尬
Because it's kind of weird.
Very nice.
想都别想 我不要去跟他讲话
- Oh, don't even think about it. - l'm gonna go talk to him.
艾玛，不
Emma, no.
我要去
l'm gonna do this.
想想你的事业，别去
Emma, think about your career. Do not do this.
梅医师
- Dr. Metzner. - Yes?
嗨，我是柯艾玛
Hi. l'm Emma Kurtzman.
我一直呵呵呵，想要… 找机会跟你聊天
l've been ho, ho, hoping that l'd get the chance to talk to you.
谁需要饮料？ 龙舌兰！
- Does anyone here need a drink? - Patron!
你们好吗？
How are you guys doing?
裘伊，加入我们！
- Joy, come join us. - Hey, Joy.
我得工作
- What's up? - l have to work.
不，坐下来
- Come on, just sit down for a second. - Sit down.
来，这里
- OK. - Come on. Here. You take that one.
我们只是在瞎混
- We're just hanging. - Thank you.
去那些客人
Screw the customers.
她超会模仿的
She is so good at impressions.
来一个模仿吧 对，来一个模仿
- Do an impression, then. - Yes, do an impression.
猜这是谁
All right, guess who this is.
爸爸！
Dad!
爸爸！ 超可爱的啦！
- Dad! - Oh, my God, that's so cute.
我不知道
- l don't know. - Come on.
你在哪里？ 我猜不出来
- Where are you? - l don't know.
你在哪里，爸爸？ 是尼莫
- Where are you, Dad? - lt's Nemo.
- Yes! - Yeah.
尼莫，我怎么会猜不到 你怎么会猜到？
- Nemo. - Amazing. l don't know why l didn't get that. How did you know that?
“海底总动员”我看了一千次
'Cause l've seen it a thousand times. That's how.
茱儿芭莉摩 我不确定我够不够醉
- Drew Barrymore. - l don't know if l'm drunk enough.
你模仿不了茱儿芭莉摩
- Come on. - You can't do Drew Barrymore.
她当然可以
Oh, but she can.
佳节愉快 我有演“婚礼歌手”哦
Happy holidays. l was in The Wedding Singer.
我只会这些了
That's it. That's all l have.
你模仿茱儿芭莉摩超不像的
That was kind of an amazing Drew Barrymore.
你连长得都很不像她
You kind of even looked like her when you did it.
裘伊，我超爱你
Oh, my God, Joy. l love you so much.
真的吗？
You do?
真的
Yeah.
丽莎，我爱你
Lisa... ...l love you.
等等 我是真的很爱你
- Wait. - l'm seriously in love with you.
你怎么不早点告诉我
Wait. Why didn't you tell me sooner?
我鼓不起勇气 天啊，这太棒了
- l didn't have the courage. - Oh, my God. This is amazing.
你超美的 你的眼睛好漂亮
- God, you look so beautiful. - And your eyes are so pretty.
- Have you got...? - Let's do this.
瓦勒斯，替我们拍照
Wallace, could you take a picture of this?
用我的手机拍
Yeah, Wallace, l got a camera right here, if you just wanna...
没问题，再靠近一点
No problem at all. Just get a little closer, ladies.
好了，大家笑一个
All right. Everybody smile.
佳节愉快！
Happy ho-lidays!
Hey, hey!
圣诞节快乐，我替你拿杯酒
Merry Christmas. Happy holidays. Can l get you a dri...?
你想离开这里吗？
You want to get out of here?
想，好啊
Yes. Yeah.
我去拿我的东西
l'll get my stuff.
听好，别跟她们上床
Listen, don't fuck one of those girls.
她们很坏，不是好东西
They're not... they're not nice. They're not nice girls.
什么？艾玛？是你吗？
What? Emma? /s that you?
凯蒂！
Katie!
你在干嘛？你在哪里？
Yeah, hi. What are you doing? Where are you?
我在为医生考试K书
l'm just studying for the doctor test.
你明天会来，对吧？
You're coming tomorrow, right?
等一下
Hold on.
嗨，亚当
Hey, Adam.
我乖乖地听你的命令
/ am fo//owing your instructions di/igent/y.
拿开啦！ 你在跟谁讲话？
- Put that away! - Who are you talking to?
你在吗？你不在，对吧？
Are you there? You're not there, are you?
计程车！计程车！
Taxi! Taxi!
带我到亚当家
Take me to Adam's house.
那在哪里？ 亚当住的地方
- OK, ma'am, where's that? - Where Adam lives.
快走，开车
- All right... - Just go. Go.
好，我这就走
OK, l'm going.
我替女士们调了鸡尾酒
Got a cocktail for the ladies.
我在模仿克里斯多夫华肯
That's my Christopher Walken.
我把饮料放在这里
Yeah. l'll just set these over here and...
然后… 我们可以一起玩3P
...then we can all sort of involve ourselves in...
OK, let's...
你们玩得很起劲耶
Well, you guys are doing a really good job.
有需要我在这里
l'll just be over here if you need me.
亚当！
Adam!
亚当法兰克林！
Adam Franklin!
亚当！法兰克林！
Adam! Franklin!
OK.
你们继续玩吧
Just keep up the good work, ladies.
你在干…？ 你是不是…？
What are...? What are you...?
Hey.
Are you...?
是，当然是
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
这是裘伊 我是裘伊，嗨
- This is Joy. - l'm Joy. Hi.
干得好 亚当？
- Good for you. - Adam?
这是丽莎
And this is Lisa.
你真是爱现鬼
You are such an overachiever.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们不需要她，叫她走
No, we don't need her. Make her leave.
不，你们走
No. You leave.
你想赶我们走？
Are you trying to get rid of us?
你长得像南瓜，婊子！
You look like a pumpkin, bitch!
太夸张了
- This is amazing. - Oh, you make... Hey!
好吧，我来处理
OK. l got this.
我会搞定，你们冷静一点
l got this. You just... calm down.
我们根本就不像南瓜
But we don't look anything like pumpkins.
我知道，她大概忘了吃药
l know. She probably forgot to take her meds.
为了安全起见，你们最好快走
You know, for your own safety, you'd better get your stuff and go.
Thanks.
小心，她可能躲起来 她超快的，就像一头美洲狮
Watch out, though. She could be anywhere. She's quick. Like a puma.
你很坏耶！
You're so mean!
铃！铃！南瓜园打来！ 他们要把南瓜叫回去！
Ring, ring! lt's the pumpkin patch! They want their pumpkins back!
我们不是南瓜！ 我们是女生！
- We're not pumpkins! - We're ladies!
可是你们全身都是橘色！
But you're so orange.
快打给仙度瑞拉！
Hey, someone call Charlie Brown!
找到南瓜马车了！
We found the Great Pumpkin!
Ow! Don't! Don't!
你疯了
You're crazy.
我觉得自己好像全民情圣
l felt like Flavor Flav.
我不敢相信你挑了那两个美眉 你在吃醋吗？
- l can't believe you chose those girls. - Are you jealous?
别这样，别突然消失不见
Don't do that. Don't just disappear like that on me.
你叫我不要见你 你该听我的
- You told me to. - You shouldn't listen to me.
好吧，我听就是了
Fine, l won't.
你在闻我的头发？ 没有
- Did you smell my hair? - No.
你想跟我谈什么？
- What did you want to talk to me about? - Wait. Just hang out here.
Right here?
Oh, man.
惊喜！
Surprise!
生日快乐！
Happy birthday!
光阴似箭、岁月如梭
只有一件事能让爹地哭泣
因为我好高兴
能当你的爸比
今天让我告诉你为什么
这是你的生日
宝贝儿子
我的小寿星
生日快乐，生日快乐
祝你生日快乐
大家一起唱！
Everybody!
祝你
生日快乐
吹蜡烛呀！ 生日快乐
Blow it out! Blow it out! Oh, Adam, happy birthday.
我们都以你为荣 许个愿
- We're so proud of you. - Make a wish.
五分钟后开拍
Guys, you get a five-minute warning.
他在厕所
- OK? - No, he's ten-one.
我刚传简讯给他
l already texted him.
所以…你原谅我了？ 不，我没原谅你
- So, all is forgiven? - No. Nothing is forgiven.
你以为我不觉得很别扭吗？
Adam, don't you think it's been weird for me, too?
知道我儿子和我女友上过床？
Knowing that... my own son had sex with my girlfriend?
但是我克服了，你也该走出来
But l got over it. You should, too.
对不起！请帮我签名！
Excuse me! Can l have your autograph, please?
我也要 没问题
- Mine, too, please. - Certainly.
我今天请你吃生日大餐
Listen, let me take you to a nice birthday dinner tonight.
你、我和凡娜莎 我们有事要告诉你
You, me and Vanessa. We have something we want to talk to you about.
有事？
- Something? - Yeah.
什么事？ 很重要的事
- Like what? - Just something important, OK?
别这样 八点整，牛排馆
- Please don't do this. - 8:20, STK.
你想带谁来就带谁来
All right? Be there. Bring anyone you want, all right?
掰了，大伙儿 多谢你肯来
- Bye, everyone. Thank you. - Oh, thank you so much for coming.
真是个荣幸
lt's been an honor.
我的老天爷！ 好耶！
- Great Scott! - Bravo! Bravo!
搞什么？
What the fuck?
- What happened? - Oh, my.
你没事吧？怎么了？
Are you OK? Are you OK? What happened?
给我！ 那是我的手机！
- Give me that! - That's my phone!
去你的，查克！ 你很有才华，但去你的！
Fuck you, Chuck! You're very talented, but fuck you!
快叫医护人员！
Can we get a medic, please?
尽量少用力
Try to use it as little as possible.
暂时别运动或健身 梅医师？
- No sports or working out for a while. - Dr. Metzner?
亚当，怎么了？怎么回事？
Adam, what's going on? What happened?
他打墙壁扭伤了手腕
He sprained his wrist punching a wall.
你传简讯说你快死了
You texted me that you were dying.
我快痛死了
lt really hurt.
我开了氢可酮，很强的止痛药
l gave him some hydrocodone for the night. lt's a very strong painkiller.
请柯医师开车送你回家
You might want to have Dr. Kurtzman here drive you home.
这是消炎药的处方笺
And here is a prescription for an anti-inflammatory.
你不会有事
Don't worry. You're in good hands.
你女友是个很好的医生
Your girlfriend here is a very talented doctor.
我不是他的女友
No. No, l'm... l'm not his girlfriend.
她不是我的女友
She is not my girlfriend.
抱歉，他把你列为紧急联络人
Oh, sorry. l saw that he listed you as an emergency contact.
我的错，早日康复
My mistake. Feel better.
对了，我很喜欢看你爸的节目
Oh, by the way, l enjoyed your dad's TV show.
我的老天爷！
Great Scott. That's funny stuff.
我会转告他的
l'll tell him you said that.
我爸请我吃晚饭
My dad invited me to dinner,
他要带凡娜莎一起去
and he's bringing Vanessa.
你得陪我去 不行
- You have to come. - No, l don't.
我值了14小时的班 我才不去见你父母
l just worked 14 hours. l'm not gonna meet your parents.
拜托，帮帮忙
You know what? Just help me.
好强的止痛药，我没有感觉
These are really powerful painkillers. l can't feel anything.
有感觉吗？
Feel that?
有，有感觉
Yeah. l felt that.
生日快乐，亚当
Happy birthday, Adam.
很高兴你能一起来
l'm so glad you guys could join us for dinner.
请慢用，我马上回来点菜
Cheers. l'll come right back to take your order.
你觉得怎样，儿子？
So, how you doing there, kiddo?
好得很，老爸，多谢关心
Perfect, Dad. Thank you for asking.
你们俩交往了多久？
How long have you two been together?
我们没有交往
Oh, we're not.
我们是饭饭之交 对，没错
- We're sex friends. - Yeah. Yes, we are.
一起炒饭的朋友？ 炮友
Yeah, friends with benefits? Fuck buddies?
我的老天爷！
Great Scott!
我知道你很难受 但我是你的前女友不代表…
l know this might be hard, but just because l'm your ex-girlfriend
你不能把我当成…妈妈
doesn't mean that you can't look at me as a kind of... mum?
天啊 尤其是我们在讨论
- Oh, boy. - Especially because, well,
想要一起创造新生命
Alvin and l have been talking about creating new life together.
我们去参加烧人节
You see, we were at Burning Man.
我们都精心打扮 我穿了火鸟装
- And we were dressed up. - Yeah. l was dressed as a fire bird.
你穿什么？
And what were you dressed as?
什么都没穿 我们在沙漠中
l was naked. And we were just out there in the desert,
他用沙子把我赤裸裸地埋起来
and he was burying my bare body in the sand.
对，用我的火鸟啄插她
Yeah. Pecking at it with my... fire beak.
然后我就想
And then l just thought,
要是这些沙子…
you know, what if all these grains of sand,
都是真的宝宝呢？
were actually babies?
于是我们… 我们有了很棒的点子
- And so we... - We had this wonderful idea.
我们希望你能祝福我们
And we... well, we'd like your blessing, Adam.
你觉得我们一起生小孩怎样？
How do you feel about the two of us having a baby together?
Adam.
我没资格说话
This isn't really my place. l mean, who am l?
我只是有时候和你儿子炒饭
l just have sex with your son sometimes.
对，没错
- But... - Yes, she does.
但是… 你们没资格把小孩带入这世界
But... there is really no reason for you to bring a child into this world,
因为你们自己就像小孩
since you're acting like children already.
你说话很毒耶
- That was really mean. - Yeah.
我说话是很毒，但你是疯子
l'm mean. But you're fucking crazy.
如果要我选择亚当或他爸
'Cause given the choice between Adam and his dad,
要我选择亚当或任何人
given the choice between Adam and anyone, really,
我一定会选择亚当
l'd choose Adam, every time.
你要走了吗？ 好
- Do you want to get out of here? - Yep.
对了
Fuck this.
我和他炒饭最爽
Oh, by the way... ...it's the best sex of my life.
我的老天爷！
Great Scott!
我得说，这是最棒的生日晚餐
l have to say, this is probably the best birthday dinner ever.
我想安排得特别一点
l wanted to make it special.
是吗？蛋糕咧？
Yeah? Where's the cake?
待会儿，宝贝
That comes later, baby.
- Hey. - What?
谢谢你在餐馆替我说话
Thank you for what you did back at the restaurant.
跟我约一次会
Go on a date with me.
你吃了太多药了
You're heavily sedated.
来嘛，跟我约一次会
Come on, it's... it's one date. Just do it.
为什么？让我化浓妆装淑女？
Why? So l can wear makeup and act perfect all night?
对
Yeah.
我开车接你，我们可以聊
l'll pick you up, and we can talk about our favorite books
我们最爱看的书和电视节目
and our favorite TV shows.
我会买单 你可以隔着
l'll pay for everything, and you can reward me
牛仔裤磨蹭我的老二
with an over-the-jeans cock rub.
就像真的约会
Like a real date.
你真的想要这样？ 这个星期五
- ls that really what you want? - This Friday.
星期五是情人节！ 不行！
This Friday is Valentine's Day. - Yeah. - No.
不然就家里蹲会有心形气球
Go big or go home. There'll be hearts,
也许会有鲜花
and maybe some flowers.
一次约会
One date.
好吧
Fine.
什么？ 我跟你约一次会
- What? - l'll go on a date with you.
我就知道你是这么说 但不准送花
- l thought that's what you said. - But no flowers, OK?
你超美的
You look amazing.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你说不准送花 这很可爱
- You said no flowers. - That's pretty cute.
这方面我很在行
Yeah, l'm pretty good at this.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我今天很累，所以… 我只想要…
l've had a really tough day, so, l just won't...
我保证会愈来愈赞
l promise. lt's about to get better.
我替你做了情人节卡片 什么？
- l made you a Valentine's Day card. - What?
太完美了
lt's perfect.
你能念给我听吗？
Can you read it for me? ls that weird?
你让我心室过早收缩
''You give me premature ventricular contractions.''
那是好事吗？ 你让我的心小鹿乱撞
- l'm assuming that's a good thing? - You make my heart skip a beat.
别笑我
- Don't make fun of me. - Wow.
你准备好了吗？ 好了
- So, you ready for tonight? - Yeah.
我很高兴见到你
l'm glad to see you.
你兴奋吗？ 兴奋
- Are you excited? - Yeah.
大声一点！ 兴奋！
- Louder! - Yeah!
我超兴奋的！
- Yeah! - So excited!
这是行程表 你做了行程表？
- Here's our itinerary. - You made me an itinerary?
很多事要做，要弥补很多时间
Yeah, we got a lot to do. We got to make up for lost time.
谷歌地图，水哦
Google Maps. Nice.
好吧，我要说实话
OK, full disclosure:
我以前打过
l have played before,
而且打得不错
and l might be kind of good.
好漂亮哦 是很漂亮
- This is pretty. - lt is pretty.
而且很好玩
- But this... it's just gonna be fun. - OK.
女士优先
Ladies first.
好吧，别期望太高
OK. Don't expect too much.
轻松自然
Nice and easy.
好耶，一杆进洞
- Yeah. l stuck it in. - Wow.
这一洞有点难度
Well, this hole's a little bit more complicated.
你得打kiss球，几何要很好
You're gonna have to bank it off there. lt's all about the geometry.
我是个医生
l'm a doctor.
又是一杆进洞！
That hole is my bitch!
Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
Thank you.
我没有自己的奶昔？
l don't get my own milkshake?
一杯奶昔，两根吸管 这才算约会
No, it's one milkshake, two straws. That's what makes it special.
可是我超饿的耶
But l'm so hungry.
待会再吃饭，你没看行程表？
We have dinner later. Didn't you read the itinerary?
你的嘴巴比较大耶
You're gonna get more shake, you have a bigger mouth.
你的嘴巴也不小 简单
You have a pretty big mouth. Oh, easy.
这算作弊
Hey! That's cheating.
抱歉
Sorry.
谢了
Thanks.
我真的很喜欢你
l really like you.
我也真的很喜欢你
我真的觉得…
l actually think that...
我爱上了…
...l'm falling...
你不如喝完吧
You can have the rest.
他们要怎么换灯泡呀？
How do they change these lightbulbs?
一定是场恶梦
Must be a nightmare.
亚当？ 你要穿大衣吗？
- Adam? - Oh, here. You want your coat?
你冷吗？
- l can take that. - You cold?
我办不到，请你载我回医院
l can't do this. Could you please take me back to work?
不是这样的
No. No, that's not the deal.
我们说好 我们一边散步
The deal is that we're gonna walk around,
一边看灯光
and we're gonna look at the twinkly lights, and then...
你干嘛要搞砸一切？
Why are you messing everything up?
一般人都这么做
That's what people do, Emma.
他们互相送花，一起逛美术馆
They buy each other flowers, and they go to museums...
你了解我 我不信那一套
You know me. This stuff freaks me out.
那全是假的
lt's fake.
我们本来那样有什么不对？ 很好呀，我们不必吵架
What's wrong with what we're doing? lt's working. We don't have to fight...
也许我想吵架 我不想
- Maybe l want to fight. - Yeah, well, l don't.
你想怎样？对谁都没感觉？
What are you gonna do? You're never gonna feel anything?
你要怎么做得到？
How you gonna do that?
不知道，我会想办法
l don't know. l'll figure it out.
你脑袋有问题 是吗？
- You're so messed up. - Yeah?
我不需要你来照顾我 我会自己照顾自己
l don't need you to take care of me. l take care of myself.
我一向都这样
That's what l do.
你何不找一个不会伤害你的女生
Why don't you go find some other girl who's not gonna hurt you?
因为我爱你
Because l love you.
太明显了，我超爱你的
lt's obvious. l completely love you. There.
你是个孬种
Oh, yeah. You're such a wimp.
才不是！ 那就跟我在一起！
- l am not a wimp. - Well, then be with me!
你要跟我打架？
OK, you're gonna fight me. Yeah? ls that what you're gonna...?
你打不过我，你是个侏儒 你就像“魔戒”的咕噜
You can't fight me, you're miniature. You're like a girl Rick Moranis.
你打起架来像只仓鼠
You fight like a hamster.
Hey. Hey!
对不起！你们不能在这里打架
Excuse me! Excuse me! You can't do that here.
好吧，对不起
OK. l'm sorry.
够了，你们出去！
All right, you're out!
我不能这样继续下去
l can't keep doing this.
我不会再见你
l'm not gonna see you again.
我知道
l know.
这样比较好
That makes sense.
再见
Bye.
你还好吧？ 我很好，谢了
- Hey, you OK? - Yeah. l'm fine, thanks.
一起去喝杯咖啡？ 不，谢了
- You wanna go get a coffee? - No, thanks.
你的厨艺真的很好耶
You're a really good cook.
我只是乱煮一通
Oh, this? l just threw it together.
该死
Oh, shit.
嗨，亚当！
Oh, hey, Adam!
亚当！你好！
Adam. Hello!
露西
Lucy.
我们在吃烛光晚餐
Yeah, we were just having a romantic night
你同事就跑来
when your friend stopped by from work.
情人节我通常都在工作 但是这么过很好玩
Usually l spend Valentine's Day catching up on work and stuff, but this is like, this is really fun.
你过得怎么样？
How was your night?
不怎么样
Yeah, it wasn't.
你要到我房间吗？
Do you want to go to my room?
好，要，太好了
Yes, l do. Perfect.
抱歉，两位，对不起
Sorry, gotta go. So sorry.
我需要餐巾，借我用一下
Oh, you know what? l need a napkin. Can l just borrow this one?
抱歉…谢谢你，你很美
Sorry. Just... quick. Thank you. Beautiful.
我能跟你聊天超兴奋的
So, l'm really excited to talk to you.
我从扣缴凭单拿到你的住址
l hope it's OK that l got your address from the W-4.
有够变态吧？
- ls that weird? OK. - No.
这地方好酷哦
Oh, wow. This is cool. This is a cool space.
谢了 很温馨
- Thanks. - Cozy.
我不知道… 抱歉
l didn't know that... l'm sorry about everything.
你在道歉？你疯了吗？
What? Oh, my God. You're sorry? Are you crazy?
我才该道歉，我不请自来耶
No, l'm sorry. l'm the one who's come to your house uninvited.
超专业的，但我看了剧本
So unprofessional. But l read your script.
我真的很喜欢 真的吗？
- And l love it. l really do. - Really?
老实说，我知道你会创作
Yeah, and honestly, like, l didn't think that you could write,
你太帅了
mainly 'cause you're just... so beautiful.
老是让我分心 谢谢你…看我的剧本
- Seriously, it's distracting for me. - Thank you. For reading it.
Yeah.
只是青少年在唱歌而已
l mean, it's just teenagers singing about homework.
对，但是我看了以后就想
Yeah, yeah, but no, l read it and l was like,
“我要到他家当面告诉他”
''God, l want to, like, drive over there and tell him in person.''
于是我就来了
So l did. l got in my car, and here l am.
我真的说出来，听起来是很疯狂
You know, it's just... l know, it sounds crazy, 'cause now that l'm saying it out loud, it does sound crazy.
并不疯狂，谢谢你看剧本
lt's not crazy. l mean, thank you for reading it.
我寄给了梅根
No, no, no. l e-mailed it to Megan, and...
真的假的？ 真的
- No shit? - Yeah.
等着看她会怎么说
- And we'll see what she says. - Wow.
我说她不喜欢就是疯子
Yeah, l told her she'd be crazy to not like it.
但她本来就是疯子，谁晓得？
But then again, she is a functioning psychotic, so it's like, who knows?
这一季结束前多出一集
But there is this extra episode right before the break.
他们要另请编剧…
And they are gonna hire a freelancer, so...
我太多话了
l feel like l'm talking too much about this, but...
你想不想…？ 什么？
- Hey, do you wanna...? - What?
你想怎样？
Yeah, sorry. What were you gonna...?
待久一点
Just to hang out.
太疯狂了，我在猜你想说什么
Oh. That's crazy. l was like, ''What's he gonna say?''
结果你这么说，跟我猜的不一样
and then you said that. lt's not what l thought you were gonna say.
那里有张椅子
That is a chair.
靠，好呀
Fuck, yeah.
我是不是太常骂脏话？
Do l curse too much?
靠，不会呀
Fuck, no.
那就好
(6星期后)
Dr. Anseed, three-two-five-one. Dr. Anseed...
- Hey. - ...three-two-five-one.
我能说句话吗？
Can l say something?
别误会
And don't take this the wrong way,
因为我永远是你朋友
because you know l'll be your friend, no matter what.
但是你最近都超沮丧的
lt's just, you've been kind of depressing to be around lately,
我可能会尽量避开你
and l might start avoiding you in the hallway, that's all.
我只想让你知道
Just thought you should know.
我们会错过婚宴试菜
So, we won't be there for the rehearsal dinner,
不过礼拜六一定会参加婚礼
but we'll definitely be there for the wedding on Saturday.
你今晚要做什么？
Well, what are you doing tonight?
亚当写的那一集今晚要录影 伊莱想去看
Adam's episode is taping tonight, so Eli wanted to go.
我不必去啦 不，去吧，玩得开心
- l don't have to go. - No. No, go. Have fun, really.
所以…？
Doctors.
So?
没关系，星期六见
Don't worry about it. l'll see you Saturday.
他是很棒的情人 天啊
- He's an amazing lover. - Oh, boy.
所以…
That's...
他的绰号才是骨头
...why they call him Bones.
我有时候会担心你
You know, l worry about you sometimes.
为什么？因为我没有男伴？
Why? ls this about me not having a date?
不，我知道你能独立自主 也知道你不会有事
No, no. l know you can dance alone, and l know that you'll be fine.
你一向都没事
You're always fine.
所以咧？ 我不知道
- So? - l don't know.
你爸去世以后 我不忍心看你那么痛苦
When we lost your father, l couldn't stand to see you in pain,
我猜你应该知道
and... l think you knew that.
我想你是为了我学会坚强
And l think that... you got good at being strong for me.
我只想告诉你，尽管伤心吧
But l'm telling you, be hurt.
我承受得了
l can take it.
这世界也承受得了
The world can take it.
好吧
OK.
这里的风景很美
Very pretty here.
你是我思念
和想在一起的人
每次你离去
我满脑子都是你
都是你
因为你是我的真爱
一直都是你
都是你
到夜店来玩，那里很热闹
So come by the bar. Great place.
带朋友来，我会罩你们
Bring your friends. l will take care of you.
我的名片，我是老板
Here's my business card. l'm the owner. Me.
一定要来玩，好吗？
- So make sure you come by. - Yeah.
干得好 是啊，干得好
All right? Hey. Great job. - Yeah, great job, man. - Really good, yeah.
你们喜欢？真的？
- You guys liked it? Like really? - Yeah.
瓦勒斯哭了 不行吗
- But Wallace cried. - So?
让我想起毕业舞会
lt reminded me of my senior prom.
我的舞伴在舞池替我口交
l got a hand job on the dance floor to ''Who Let The Dogs Out.''
抱歉，有好消息和坏消息
Hey. Sorry. OK, so there's good news, bad news.
坏消息是梅根醉到不行
The bad news is, Megan is remarkably drunk.
她想扯掉她的衬衫
Seriously, she was, like, trying to take her shirt off.
好消息是她想让你当固定编剧
But the good news is, she wants to put you on staff.
真的吗？
- Really? - So... Yeah.
棒呆了！
- That's amazing. - Yeah, so she... Yeah.
谢谢你 你是正式的编剧了
- Thank you. - So, you're a paid writer.
Yeah.
天啊，她要站上自助吧台
Oh, my God. She's getting on the buffet table? That makes...
Wow.
你干嘛不试着跟她炒饭？
Why are you not trying to fuck that girl?
Yeah.
她超辣的，就像火辣的科学家
Yeah, she's crazy hot, Adam. She's like a sexy scientist.
你得Man一点放马过去
You need to go over there, man up, you need to go for it.
我们就看你的了，Man一点！
We're counting on you here, man. Man up, man!
去吧！Man一点！ Man一点？
- Go for it! Man up! - You keep saying ''Man up.''
你刚才哭了耶 我很感动嘛
- You cried during the show. - l liked the show.
你吃过蛋糕吗？
吃过，还…还好啦
Yeah. - lt was very good. - lt was OK.
我得…等一下
You know, l have to... One minute.
凯蒂？
Katie?
伴娘有大麻
The bridesmaids had pot.
天啊，我超饿的！
Oh, my God, l'm so hungry.
你还好吧？
Are you OK?
我很好，只是…
l'm fine, l just... You know, l just...
天啊，我超爱凯文的
Oh, God, l just love Kevin.
我超爱凯文
l just love Kevin so much, you know?
你一定觉得很傻 不，不会
- l know you think it's stupid. - No. No, l don't.
不会吗？ 不会
- You don't? - No.
我没办法不想他
l can't stop thinking about him.
谁？亚当？
Who? Adam?
我们结束了，我也在找男人
Yeah. l know it's over, and l'm looking.
只是没有人像他那么…
lt's just no one is as...
那么高？ 他超高的
- Tall? - He's so tall.
而且他一直都很…
- So tall... - And he's so, like...
开心？ 随时都很开心，超讨厌的
- Happy? - Annoyingly happy, all the time.
不过他有一颗…
But he has this...
他有一颗最善良的心
He has the best heart.
打给他 什么？
- Call him. - What? No.
我才不要打给他
l can't just call him.
我太high了，别跟我吵
l'm too stoned. Don't argue with me.
他不要我打给他
He doesn't want me to call him.
我是新娘，你得听我的话
l'm the bride. You have to do what l say.
我们有几个月没说话
- We haven't talked in months. - l'm the bride, it's my day.
今天我最大！
lt's my day!
嗨，亚当！
Hey, Adam!
天啊
Oh, God.
你超赞的，你自己知道吗？
You're so dope. Did you know that about yourself?
妈妈要坐计程车回家
Mama needs to get a cab home, so...
我的手机在办公室
- Yeah. - Shoot, l left my phone in my office...
等一下
l got it, l got it. Hang on. Here.
你要打电话？
- Do you want to call and just...? - Yeah.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
查克！查克！给我滚开！
Chuck! Chuck! Will you please fuck off? Please?
我不想走
- l don't want to go. - Yeah, all right.
我不想回家 是谁？
l don't want to go home. - l don't want to go home. - Who is it?
“别打给她”打来了 你要接吗？
''Do Not Call Her'' is calling. Do you want to take it?
l want your face.
喂？
He//o?
Hi.
我是艾玛，夏令营的柯艾玛
lt's Emma. Kurtzman. From Camp Weehawken.
是，什么事？
Yes... What is it?
我妹明天要在圣塔芭芭拉结婚
So, my sister is getting married in Santa Barbara tomorrow, and...
听说你的节目今晚录影，恭喜了
/ don't know. / heard your show is tonight. Congratu/ations.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我知道这很突然，我只是…
l know this is random. l just...
我很想你，我超哈你的
l miss you. l miss you so much.
好吧
OK.
我不知道该说什么
l don't know what to say.
你去参加你妹的婚礼
You're... You're calling me because you're at your sister's wedding,
她很开心
and she looks happy, and...
大家都很开心 只有你不开心
...everyone is happy, and you're not.
我以为…我不知道在想什么…
l thought... l don't know what l thought. l just...
我猜我只想听到你的声音
l... l guess l wanted to hear your voice.
我知道我们分手了
- l mean, l know we broke up, but... - Emma.
我们没有分手 我们根本没有交往
We didn't break up. We never started.
我得走了，我在工作
/ gotta go. /'m sti// at work, so...
玩得开心点 替我向你妹妹说声恭喜
Have fun at the wedding, and tell your sister congratulations.
掰了
Bye.
靠
Oh, fuck.
我得…
l have to...
去吧
- Go. - Now.
我能不能…？ 当然可以
- Hey. Can l? - Hey. Of course.
一切还好吧？
ls everything OK? Are you...?
还好
Yeah.
很好！ 那就好
- Yeah. Yes. - Yeah. Good.
太不可思议了
- This is amazing. - Yeah.
谢谢你…替我做的一切
Thank you for this. This...
这全是你的功劳
- What? - This was all you.
什么？没啦 没有你我就不会成功
- What? No, l mean... - No, l'm not here without you.
才不是，是你自己很有才华
That's... That's not true. lt's all you. lt's all you. This was all you.
等一下，如果你来不及赶回来 参加婚礼，我会杀了你
Hey, wait! lf you don't make it back for my wedding, l'll kill you.
小心开车
Bye. Drive safe.
No, but that was you, and it felt poignant
that, of course, the song was ''lt Was You.''
- When Benji and Sari did the kiss... - They committed to it.
这首歌能重新混音吗？
That's what hit. Do you think they could remix the song?
梅根想上我的腿
How drunk was Megan? She tried to hump my leg.
你不知道太多她的事了
You have no idea, the stories that l could tell you.
她真的想跨上我的腿
- No, she really tried to like mount it. - Yeah, l know.
Yeah, l got it.
Ornery thing.
怎样？找到他吗？
Hey. How'd it go? Did you find him?
他跟一个女的在一起，他的女友
Yeah. He was with... with a girl. lt was his girlfriend.
我躲在草丛里
And l was in a bush.
- Oh. - Yeah.
讨厌
Crap.
你还在吗？ 在
- Are you sti// there? - Yeah.
上车，马上开走
OK, get in your car and drive away.
你身上有多少钱？
And how much money do you have on you?
十块钱
Like ten bucks.
一盒50粒甜甜圈洞是$5.79
OK. The box of 50 doughnut holes is $5.79.
你会需要两盒
You're gonna need two boxes.
我失去他了
l lost him.
真是遗憾
- /'m so sorry. - Yeah.
我爱你
- / /ove you. - l know.
我知道 我11岁那年去看心理医生
So, then when l was, like, 1 1 , l was in therapy
因为我不停地咬头发
because l was, like, obsessively biting my hair,
3个月后医生就挂了
and then three months in, my therapist died.
我真的很难过
- l know, so that was kind of a bummer. - Whoa.
所以我讨厌搭飞机
But, yeah. That's why l hate planes.
Thanks.
这就是我的故事 干杯
- So, that's that story. - Cheers.
Thank you.
对不起
- l'm so sorry. - No...
我太笨手笨脚了
- That was such a fail on my part. - lt's OK...
等一下
- Wait, let me... - lt's fine.
我可以做得更好
We can... l can do better than that.
重新再来 欧麦尬
- Can we try again? - Sure. Mulligan.
- Let's... Why don't we...? - OK.
All right.
真的发生了
Oh, my God. This is happening. ls this really happening?
我真的在跟你亲嘴耶
Oh, my God. You're touching me. This is so happening.
也许你不必什么都说出来
Maybe we don't need to talk about everything.
好，很好，酷
Oh. OK, great. OK. Cool.
你确定你真的要这样？
Wait. Are you sure that you want to do this, though?
我确定
Yes. Yeah.
我们可以先讨论
OK, 'cause, like, we can just talk about it, if you want...
不用讨论
- Let's not talk about it. - Oh, OK. OK.
我要自己脱，还是你帮我脱？
Wait. Should l take my shirt off, or do you want to... Do you want to take it off yourself?
我帮你脱 我还是自己脱好了
- l'll take it off. - You know what? l'll take it off.
OK.
幸好我穿了性感胸罩
Glad l wore a good bra.
那是你的手机吗？
ls that your phone? Do you wanna...?
别管它
We'll just ignore it.
你可以去接
You can just get it.
没关系
No, it's fine.
是不是“别打给她”？ 不是
- ls it ''Do Not Call Her''? - No.
我不知道
l don't know.
等一下，我去…
Wait. l'll just...
我把手机关掉
- OK. - l'll just shut it off.
这样比较简单
Yeah, just... That'll be easier, switch...
抱歉
- Sorry. - Yeah.
凡娜莎？
Vanessa?
我马上来 怎么了？
- l'm coming. - You're what?
我爸出了事，他在医院
lt's my dad. There's an emergency. He's in the hospital.
天啊，你要我陪你去吗？
Oh, my God. OK. Do you want me to go with you?
不，我自己去
- No, l'm OK. - OK.
我晚点再打给你？ 好，我叫车…我自己会回家
- Can l call you later? - Yeah. No, l'll get a cab. l'll, like, find my way home. Go. Yeah.
他们并不知道真相
我的心被血管堵塞
我一直关紧着心房
但你把我的心切开
我一直，一直流爱的血
(打给我！)
他在哪里？怎么回事？
Hey. Where is he? What happened?
OK.
别抓狂，好吗？
Don't freak out, OK?
你爸服用咳嗽糖浆过量
Your dad overdosed on cough syrup.
什么？ 紫药水
- He what? - The Purple Drank.
紫药水？
''The Purple Drank''?
七喜、咳嗽糖浆加糖果
lt's Seven-Up, cough syrup and a Jolly Rancher.
他干嘛喝这种玩意儿？
Why would he do that, Vanessa?
他超爱饶舌歌手小韦恩！
Because he loves Lil Wayne, OK?
你知道你爸的一切
You don't know everything about your dad.
你干嘛逼他听小韦恩？
Why are you making him listen to Lil Wayne?
你应该照顾他 我办不到
- You should be taking care of him. - l can't do this. l can't do it.
我不知道会这么…
You know, l didn't think that it was gonna be so...
我不想生小孩，我只想玩乐
l don't want to have kids. l... l just... l want to have fun.
他好老哦 对，他会变得更老
- He's so old. - Yeah. He's getting older.
你得面对这事实
And you're gonna have to deal with that.
亚当…老人让我害怕
Adam... old people scare me.
我们去见他，好吗？
Let's just go see him, OK?
不，我不行，我得走了
No, no, no. l can't. l can't. Adam, l can't. l've gotta go.
我朋友开轰趴，我迟到了
My friend, she's having a party. l'm already so late.
把斑斑拿去
Will you just take Freckles?
别误会哦，不过你是个大烂人
Don't take this the wrong way, but you're a terrible person.
把斑斑拿去
Just take Freckles.
嗨，爸
Hey, Dad.
嗨，儿子
Hey, kiddo.
我喝了紫药水不舒服 我听说了
- l had a bad trip on The Drank. - Yeah, l heard.
有人问就说这是导盲犬
lf anybody asks, this is a Seeing Eye dog.
她人呢？ 她回家了
- Where's...? - She went home.
才怪
Right.
我不爱听小韦恩，听不懂歌词
l really don't like the Little Wayne. Can't understand what he's saying.
你知道我希望谁在这里？
You know who l wish was here right now?
你妈
Your mom.
你离开她
Yeah. Well, you left her, so...
为什么？
Why?
当你结婚后又吸古柯碱
When you're married and you do blow...
最好离漂亮妹远一点
...try to stay away from women who want to fuck you.
就连恐龙妹也一样
Even ugly women.
吸毒让人盲目，吸毒让人盲目
Blow is blind, Adam. Blow is blind.
你是个大混蛋
You're an asshole.
但你不是
But you're not.
你有一颗善良的心 保持它
You got a good heart, Adam. Try to keep it.
艾玛呢？你们没在一起吗？
Where's that girl, Emma? You guys still together?
我们从来没有在一起过 对哦，只是朋友
- We were never together. - Oh, that's right. Friends...
炮友？我老了，不知道叫什么
Sex friends... l'm old. l don't know what you call it.
但是你喜欢她
You liked her.
她让我抓狂
She drives me crazy.
我58岁了，结过3次婚
l'm 58 years old. l've been married three times.
两次
Twice.
好吧
OK.
我的手机有6张我老二的照片
l've got six pictures of my cock on my phone,
还有两张别人的老二
and two of someone else's,
而且我现在还是很high
and l'm still pretty high on the cough syrup,
你不听也罢，但是…
so you can take this with a grain of salt, but...
我们不能选择我们爱上的人
...we don't pick who we fall in love with.
爱情没有任何规则
And it never happens like it should.
Yes.
我也许得杀死这只狗 我还没决定怎么杀
l may have to kill this dog. l just haven't decided how.
睡点觉吧，爸
Get some sleep, Dad.
我一早再打给你
l'll call you in the morning.
他一早不会打给我
He'll call in the morning.
不错吧？
lsn't that something?
我让你很无聊？
Am l boring you?
那就好
Oh, good.
亚当！
Adam!
你不能打给我说你很想我
Hey. You can't call me and tell me that you miss me.
我不想在电话上讨论
l don't want to have that conversation on the phone.
你不能传简讯或电子邮件
So you can't text me and you can't e-mail me,
也不能在我的涂鸦墙留言
and you can't... write on my wall.
如果你真的很想我 就得成熟一点
Like, if you really miss me, you need to grow up
开车来见我
and get in your car and come and see me.
我来了
l'm here.
你怎么知道…
How did... How did you know that...?
希拉传简讯告诉我，我就来了
Shira texted me about your dad, so l came here.
You got...
你爸怎样？
How is your dad?
他没事 那就好
- He's OK. - Good.
我知道我不能光是打给你 对，没错
- l know l can't just call you. - No. You can't.
我知道 我伤了你的心，对不起
l know. l hurt you. l'm sorry.
我浪费太多时间假装我在乎
l don't know why l wasted so much time pretending l didn't care.
我猜我想像现在这样
l guess l just didn't want to feel like this.
这么伤心
lt hurts.
但是我完完全全地爱你
But l love you. l'm totally and completely in love with you,
就算你觉得太迟了我还是要说
and l don't care if you think it's too late, l'm telling you anyway.
你能不说些什么？ 等一下
- Will you please say something? - Wait.
你要知道
You should know...
如果你再靠近一点
...if you come any closer,
我就不会放你走
l'm not letting you go.
我爱你 很好
- l love you. - That's good.
想陪我参加很蠢的场合吗？
You want to go with me to this stupid thing?
你老妹的婚礼？
Your sister's wedding thing?
开车过去要多久？
How long do we have till we have to be there?
两个小时
A couple hours.
你想做什么？ 疯狂的事
- What do you want to do? - Something crazy.
我终于知道你不肯跟我吃早餐
Now l know why you never wanted to have breakfast with me.
What?
你像只恐龙宝宝 连咬都不咬
You eat like a baby dinosaur. You don't even chew.
你能习惯吗？
Do you think you can get used to it?
应该可以
Yeah, l think so.
很好，我想常常跟你吃早餐
Good. l was hoping we could do this a lot more.
真的吗？ 我在想哦
Really? You know, l was thinking...
我们得建立新的规则
We're gonna have to come up with some new rules.
我想开始叫你甜心或宝贝
l'd like to start calling you ''honey'' and ''babe.''
叫宝贝不太好 不好？
- l don't know about ''babe.'' - No?
玩抱抱呢？ 可以
- Snuggling? - Oh, yeah.
我会要牵你的手 哇，进展得太快了吧
- l'm gonna hold your hand. - Wow. This is all moving so fast.
我尿尿的时候都关门
Also, l'd like to leave the door open when l pee.
不行
l think no.
我会常常这样 我们的关系会变得很怪
l think l'm gonna do it all the time. lt's gonna get weird.
谢天谢地我们赶到了
- Thank God we're on time. - Yeah.
现在怎么样？
So what happens now?
亚当随时都会到 太好了，我饿扁了
- Adam should be here any minute. - Good, 'cause l'm starving.
你跟他说过我们的事了吧
So, you've told him about us.
还没有
- No, not yet. - What?
我想等他来了再说
l thought l'd wait till he got here.
那样好吗？ 没问题
- And that's a good idea? - Yeah, it'll be fine.
敬烧人节
So, to Burning Man?
好不好玩？ 超好玩的
- Was that fun, or what? - So fun.
爸！
Dad!
伊莱！
Eli!
这就是派翠丝！
This is her! This is Patrice!
很高兴再见到你们
Hi, it's so nice to see you again.
我们已经很爱你了！ 家人抱抱！
- We love you already! - Come on, family hug!
我觉得我还有未开发的地方
Shira, l feel like there are parts of me that l haven't explored yet.
我想和别人约会
And l'm feeling like l want to see other people.
我以为…这真尴尬
Oh, l thought... This is embarrassing.
我已经有跟别人约过会了
l have been seeing other people, Sam.
真的吗？ 超多人的
- You have? - Yeah, a lot of other people.
多少人？
How many?
不知道，我一下只想到两个人
l don't know, man. l mean, two that l can think of off the top of my head, but...
你记得我去度假吗？
- You remember when l went to Cabo? - Yeah.
我一路上都是个荡妇 你在开玩笑吧
- l was a very bad girl on that trip. - You're kidding me?
你做得很好
You're doing great.
继续用力！
Keep pushing.
噢，天啊
Oh, God.
老婆，我有冰块
l've got the ice chips, honey. Here you go.
我恨你，大笨蛋，滚出去
Oh, l hate you, you dumb fuck! Get the fuck out...
给我把冰块吃掉！ 我爱你
- You eat the fucking ice chips! - l love you so much.
来吧，安啦
Come on. lt's OK.
MANDARIN ENGLlSH ESL